## CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

# UX/UI Designer

## CONTACT

✓ Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

A Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

#### SKILLS

Design Psychology Front End -

Figma Web Development

Wireframes HTML

Prototyping CSS

User Research JavaScript (JS)

Sketching Node.js

Data Synthesis Git

Usability Testing Bootstrap

Journey Mapping Material UI

React.js

Adobe Creative Angular.js

## **EDUCATION**

Human Computer
Interaction for UX (Cert.)

MIT xPRO

**UI** Design

UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

#### PROFILE

Hi, a bit about me I'm a passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill user needs. A capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. A UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain points, and behaviors.

## EXPERIENCE

## **Application Development Analyst**

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
  - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
- Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

#### **Brand Strategist**

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies.
- Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
  - lead to 50% contract signing increase.

#### **All-Source Intelligence Technician**

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- Supervision
  - Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
  - Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
  - Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research